

Denver, CO

((203) - 240 - 9108

samvredenburgh.com/

github.com/uelski

in linkedin.com/in/samvredenburgh

Summary

Originally from the Northeast, I am a web developer who now calls Colorado home. I enjoy problem solving and creating beautiful things, from web applications, to paintings and music.

Skills

Web Development

Javascript, HTML/CSS, Angular, Polymer, Meteor, Express, Node.js, Firebase, Google App Engine, AWS

Development Experience

Whirlpool Corporation

Developed many web experiences including landing pages, interactive campaigns, IoT application front-end, and custom AEM web components

www.stdexpresscheck.com

User facing e-commerce site built with Angular, HTML/SASS, Gulp - deployed through Google App Engine

www.masoncos.com

Website for my band built with create-react-app and deployed on Heroku

Internal Twilio App

Node/Express app with Twilio API for phone/text use, connected with Pusher WebSocket API - deployed through AWS

Work History

Front End Developer

May 2017 - Present

ARS

Worked with cross-agency teams to develop and deliver web experiences for multiple brands using modern web technologies including AEM, Wordpress, VueJS, AngularJS, NuxtJS, SCSS and HTML5

Web Developer

May 2016 - April 2017

TSG Medical Group

Built upon existing code and created new applications to expand e-commerce systems

Architect Reporter

Feb 2012 - Aug 2015

BidClerk, Inc.

Construction industry project database - researched, created and updated projects

Education

Web Development Immersive

Oct 2015 - Jan 2016

General Assembly

Experience creating web applications using Node, Express, Backbone, MongoDB, Ruby on Rails and PostgresSQL

Bachelor of Arts

Aug 2007 - May 2011

University of Vermont

Major: Economics, Minor: Music